RILEY WEBER-HOROWITZ

STUDENT COMMUNICATIONS & EVENTS COORDINATOR

CONTACT

(513)550-1018

rileywh13@outlook.com

weberhoror2@mymail.nku.edu

EDUCATION

Northern Kentucky University

Double Bachelor of Arts in Public Relations and 3D Digital Design & VFX 2022-Present

Campbell County High School

2018-2022

REFERENCES

Larissa Heck | Manager,
Communication, Events, and
Administration
Northern Kentucky University,
College of Informatics
E: heckl3@nku.edu
P: (859) 572-5666

SKILLS

- Mentoring
- Teaching
- Multitasking
- · Problem-solving
- Adaptability
- Teamwork

ABOUT ME

I'm an avid communicator with a strong background in organizing and leadership. I've volunteered my time throughout my whole life to creating opportunities for K-12 students through a variety of organizations and personal work. My experiences with community volunteering and outreach have made me a passionate and dedicated communicator with a love for helping others. I'm a confident public speaker and an innovative problem solver.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

College of Informatics - Northern Kentucky University

Student Communications & Events Coordinator | Feb 2023 - Current

- Web editor for the Informatics website, assisted with website redesign.
- Manages all social media accounts of the college, boosting engagement
- Provides photography, videography, and communication needs.
- · Helps plan events for the College of Informatics
- Provides content for internal & external communications

Center for Integrative Natural Science and Mathematics (CINSAM) Cyber Academy

Teaching Assistant | May 2024 - June 2024

- Collaborated with fellow CINSAM teaching assistants to plan, design and organize all instructional materials
- Delivered engaging instructional content to CINSAM cyber camp students
- Mentored high school students through several educational cybersecurity games, activities and workshops
- Provided swift, effective and positive conflict resolution when required

RECENT VOLUNTEERING - LIST OF ORGANIZATIONS

Additional details available upon request

- INTERalliance TechOlympics
- Campbell County 4-H
- Matthew 25 Ministries (Humanitarian Aid)
- Campbell County Band of Pride